[
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Hello. My name ___ John.",
			"optionA":"is",
			"optionB":"are",
			"optionC":"be",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Which city ___ you from?",
			"optionA":"is",
			"optionB":"are",
			"optionC":"am",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Hi. ___ you American?",
			"optionA":"Am",
			"optionB":"Is",
			"optionC":"Are",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Peter ___ the tallest boy in class.",
			"optionA":"is",
			"optionB":"are",
			"optionC":"be",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"What time ___ it?",
			"optionA":"am",
			"optionB":"is",
			"optionC":"be",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I ___ Italian.",
			"optionA":"be",
			"optionB":"is",
			"optionC":"am",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"When will the party ___?",
			"optionA":"be",
			"optionB":"is",
			"optionC":"are",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"What ___ New York like?",
			"optionA":"are",
			"optionB":"is",
			"optionC":"be",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Sean and Anna ___ 20 years old.",
			"optionA":"be",
			"optionB":"is",
			"optionC":"are",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I am going to ___ there.",
			"optionA":"be",
			"optionB":"is",
			"optionC":"are",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I hope there ___ no snow tomorrow.",
			"optionA":"be",
			"optionB":"is",
			"optionC":"are",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"There ___ many stores in this little village.",
			"optionA":"be",
			"optionB":"is ",
			"optionC":"are",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"___ there a market in this town?",
			"optionA":"is",
			"optionB":"are",
			"optionC":"be",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"___ there flowers in the park?",
			"optionA":"is",
			"optionB":"Are",
			"optionC":"Be",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"There will ___ a party tomorrow.",
			"optionA":"are",
			"optionB":"is",
			"optionC":"be",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	}
]